A Finding Aid to the 55 Mercer Artists, Inc. Records, 1939-2007, bulk 1970-2007, in the Archives of American Art AAA.55mercga
Archives of American Art
55 Mercer Artists, Inc. records
bulk 1970-2007
1939-2007
AAA.55mercga
Archives of American Art
5.1 Linear feet
55 Mercer Artists, Inc. records, 1939-2007, bulk 1970-2007, measure 5.1 linear feet. The records, which are incomplete with sizeable gaps, consist of administrative records, exhibition files, artists’ files, financial records, scrapbooks, guest books, and printed material that document one of the most successful and long lived artist run cooperative galleries in SoHo. The only item pre-dating 55 Mercer Artists, Inc. is a 1939 newspaper clipping in the artists' files.
55 Mercer Street Artists, Inc.
Immediate Source of Acquisition note
Donated in 2007 by 55 Mercer Street Artists, Inc. via Ethelyn Honig.
Restrictions on Access
Use of original material requires an appointment.
Arrangement
The collection is arranged as 7 series:
Series 1: Administrative Records, circa 1970-2007 (Box 1; 0.4 linear ft.)
Series 2: Exhibition Files, 1971-2007 (Box 1; 0.4 linear ft.)
Series 3: Artists' Files, 1939, 1973-2006 (Boxes 1-2; 0.6 linear ft.)
Series 4: Financial Records, 1973-2006 (Boxes 2-3; 0.8 linear ft.)
Series 5: Scrapbooks, 1977-1987 (Box 3; 0.3 linear ft.)
Series 6: Guest Books, 1972-2007 (Boxes 3-5; 1.7 linear ft.)
Series 7: Printed Material, 1973-2007 (Box 5, OV 6; 0.9 linear ft.)
Biographical/Historical note
55 Mercer Artists, Inc., an artist-run alternative to commercial galleries, was founded as 55 Mercer Gallery - also known as 55 Mercer Street Gallery and 55 Mercer - in December 1969. The earliest of a second wave of co-operative galleries in New York City, it was one of the most successful and the longest lived.
Many of the founders and early members were active in the Art Workers’ Coalition, a group formed to address artists’ rights issues and promote the overhaul of the museum and gallery system to remove profit motives from art. Tom Parker, an artist friend acting on behalf of group members who aspired to open a co-operative gallery, rented the third floor of 55 Mercer Street. He reserved a room to use as a studio and sublet the remainder to the co-op. Two large galleries of nearly equal size were separated by a small, open office area, a layout that led to a tradition of tandem solo exhibitions or one large group show. The open, spare and worn space especially appealed to sculptors and attracted those who worked in large scale with recycled materials.
The inaugural exhibition in early 1970 was a group show of the ten founding members: Alice Adams, Martin Bressler, Don Cole, Gloria Greenburg, Stan Kaplan, Christy Park, Stephen Rosenthal, L. Shreve Stevenson, and Merrill Wagner; during the first year, each member also had a solo exhibition. With haphazard arrangements and no publicity or gallery guide listings, reviews were not forthcoming. Nevertheless, by the end of its first year the gallery had established a reputation as a space “of artists, by artists, and for artists” and over the years presented some of the best exhibitions in SoHo. Membership was fluid. No particular style or philosophy was ever dominant, and members found unity in their focus on quality, antipathy to commercial galleries and insistence on freedom for member and guest artists alike.
By the start of its second season, the gallery had the attention of critics and reviews were appearing regularly in art periodicals. When the co-operative gallery Ours closed at the end of 1970, Janet Fish, Diane Karol, Paul Tschinkel, and Frank Lincoln Viner were invited to join. With larger membership came the need for a definite exhibition schedule and greater organization. Over the next few years, meetings began to occur more frequently. By the mid 1970s the gallery began to receive funding from sources such as the New York State Council on the Arts and the National Endowment for the Arts.
Officially incorporated as 55 Mercer Street Artists, Inc. in 1977, the organizations by-laws specified: “The corporation is a not-for-profit corporation whose purpose is to provide a facility for artists who seek to introduce their work to the public. The corporation maintains an exhibition space which it makes available for this purpose, both for its artists members, and for visiting artists. In addition, the corporation presents performances, discussions, workshops and other art-related events for the general public.” A board of directors composed of artist members managed the affairs of the corporation assisted by a Membership Committee, Grants Committee, and Selection Committee that chose and scheduled exhibitions,
Trustees began managing the building after the owner of the 55 Mercer Street died, and 55 Mercer Artists, Inc. received an eviction notice in early 2007. Legal representation was obtained and a loophole discovered, but declining membership and the poor physical condition of the facilities eventually prompted a decision to relocate. Some members chose to join other galleries. A core group of about a dozen 55 Mercer artists found a suitable space in Long Island City; after reorganizing as an artist-initiated not-for-profit gallery, they reopened in 2008 as M55 Mercer Art.
Scope and Contents note
55 Mercer Artists, Inc. records, 1939-2007, bulk 1970-2007, measure 5.1 linear feet. The records, which are incomplete with sizeable gaps, consist of administrative records, exhibition files, artists’ files, financial records, scrapbooks, guest books, and printed material that document one of the most successful and long lived artist run cooperative galleries in SoHo. The only item pre-dating 55 Mercer Artists, Inc. is a 1939 newspaper clipping in the artists' files.
Administrative records include correspondence, records of board committees, exhibition schedules, membership and mailing lists, and minutes. Exhibition files consist of slides and photographs of installations and individual works of art, small amounts of correspondence, notes, and lists of works shown.
Artists’ files consist of various combinations of correspondence, resumes, printed material, photographs and slides of art work of members and guest artists. Many artists are represented by just an item or two; files for Corliss Cavaliere, Peter Charlap, Joan Gardner, Irene Gennaro, Jon Gregg, Ethelyn Honig, and Lisa Ingram are more substantial.
The majority of financial records concern membership dues, rent and exhibition fees received. Also included are sporadic banking records, paid bills, treasurers' reports, insurance information and tax records. Eight scrapbooks include exhibition announcements, publicity, reviews, miscellaneous printed material, photographs, and slides.
Guest books consist of 22 volumes and loose pages that record gallery visitors, many of whom offered comments about the shows. Exhibition titles and dates are noted on the page for the day of each opening reception.
Among the printed materials are exhibition announcements, catalogs, and publicity produced by 55 Mercer Artists, Inc.; copies of every exhibition announcement, catalog, and press release issued have not survived. Also found are articles about or mentioning 55 Mercer Artists, Inc., exhibition reviews, advertisements and event listings.
55 Mercer St. Gallery; Charlap, Peter, 1949-; Gardner, Joan; Genaro, Irene; Gregg, Jon; Honig, Ethelyn; Ingram, Lisa; Alternative spaces (Art facilities)--New York (State)--New York; Art galleries, Commercial--New York (State)--New York; Art galleries, Cooperative--New York (State)--New York; Photographs; Scrapbooks; Visitors' books
- Administrative Records, circa 1970-2007; Series 1; 0.4 Linear feet Box 1
  Scope and Contents note
  Among the administrative records are correspondence, records of board committees, exhibition schedules, membership and mailing lists, and minutes. These records are incomplete, with sizeable gaps throughout. Correspondence consists of letters and copies of e-mail to and from various officers and members regarding fairly routine matters related to the gallery operations. Of particular interest is a letter dated February 2, 2007, concerning eviction notices received by tenants of 55 Mercer Street and ideas about where the co-op might relocate. Interfiled with minutes are meeting notices, agendas, correspondence, and various documents relating to business discussed.
  - By-Laws, circa 1977 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Committees (Box 1)
    - General Information, undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Grants Committee - Private Foundation Research, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Grants Committee - Citibank, Jerome Foundation, and Lannan Foundation Grants, 1983-1987 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Grants Committee, Private Foundation Research, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Grants Committee, National Endowment for the Arts Grants, 1980- 1987, undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Grants Committee - National Endowment for the Arts Grants, undated; 1980-1987 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Grants Committee - New York City, Department of Cultural Affairs Emergency Funding, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Grants Committee - New York State Council on the Arts, undated; 1975-1985 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Membership Committee, Contracts and Correspondence, 1992-2005 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Selection Committee - Report; Gallery Information for Exhibitors, 1986-2006; undated (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Selection Committee - Letters of Intent and Show Contracts, 1995-2001 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Selection Committee - Applications; Exhibition Proposals, 1984-2000; undated (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Competitions and Opportunities, 1973-2007; undated (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence, 1983-2007 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Exhibition Schedules and Lists, undated; 1973-2007 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Floor Plans of Gallery, undated (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - History, undated; circa 1970-1999 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Landlord, 1973-1992; undated (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Mailing Lists, 1990s-2004; undated (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Membership Lists, undated; 1980-2002 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Minutes, 1974-1996 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Minutes, undated; 1997-2005 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Exhibition Files, 1971-2007; Series 2; 0.4 Linear feet Box 1
  Exhibition files include slides and photographs of exhibition installations and individual works of art exhibited. Some files also contain small amounts of correspondence, notes, and lists of works shown.
  Arrangement note
  Related material is included among the administrative records (series 1), especially in the Selection Committee's correspondence. Financial records (series 4) document exhibition fees paid by member and guest artists. Exhibition announcements, catalogs, press releases and reviews are found with printed material (series 7) and in the scrapbooks (series 5). Guest books (series 6) verify dates of exhibitions and record shows for which there is no other surviving documentation.
  - Christy Park Installation (1971) (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Robert Rodrigues Installation (1975 September) (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - "Donna Byars" and "Richard Thatcher" (1975 October 4-22) (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - "J. Nebraska Gifford" and "Gail von der Lippe" (1976 September 4-22) (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - "Merrill Wagner" (1976 October 16-November 3) (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - "Ivan Biro" and "Helen Soreff" (1977 January 8-26) (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - "Alan Finkel" (April 23-May 11), 1978 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - "Joel Tobias" (1978 September 12-30) (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - "Upper New York State Artists" (1981 January 14-31) (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - "Fred Gutzeit" (1981 November 10-28) (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - "Joyce Robins" (1981 December 1-19) (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - South Dakota Artists (1982 August-September), 1983 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - "55 Mercer: 12 Years" (1983 January 12-February 5) (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Urban Girls Show (1983 June) (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Summer Invitational Show (1984 June 19-July 7) (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - "#2 Smart Art Too" (1985 January 8-26) (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - "Chain Reaction" (1985 December 17-1986 January 4) (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - "Gar Wang" (1996 September 30-October 18), 1986 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - "Judy Linn" (1986 October 21-November 8) (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Sculpture Group Show (1986 December 23-1987 January 10) (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - "Dan Bufano; Erik Derkatsch" (1987 January 11-31) (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - "Eliot Lable" (1987 February 2-20) (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - "Florence Neal; Scott Pfaffman" (1987 February 3-21) (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - "George Grant" (1987 April) (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - "Color Renaissance" (1987 June 9-27) (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - "Michael Cochran; Justine Trueger" (1987 June 30-July 25) (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - "David Hale; Sarah Jackson; Stanford Kay; Scott White" (1987 July 28-August 22) (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - "Diane Karol; Carol Parlato" (1987 September 8-26) (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - "Betty Beaumont: Toxic Imaging; Ray Rapp" (1987 September 29-October 17) (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - "Jill Barof; Gar Wang" (1987 October 20-November 7) (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - "Bob Chaplin; Judy Linn" (1987 November 10-28) (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - "1987 Christmas Invitational Group Exhibition" (1987 December 22-1987 January 9), 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - "Tomatsu Shiihara" (1988 February) (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - "20th Anniversary Exhibition" (1990 December) (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Friends Show (1988 September 8-26), 1998 (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - "Digital Traces" (circa 1999 or later) (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Black Fish Gallery [Portland, OR] Group Exhibition (2006 August 6-26) (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - 2007 June, "Phantom Limb," Rhode Island School of Design MFA Photography Show; "Rainbow Sins," Rhode Island School of Design MFA Printmaking Show Show (2007 June 19-30) (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - Sculpture Group Show [Howard McCalebb, curator] (undated, January 5-23) (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - Summer Invitational Show (undated June-July) (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - "Intellects and Idiosyncrasies: An Exhibition of Sculpture; Unidentified Installation" (undated) (Box 1, Folder 62)
- Artists' Files, 1939; 1973-2006; Series 3; 0.6 Linear feet Boxes 1-2
  Artists’ files include various combinations of correspondence, resumes, printed material, photographs and slides of art work.
  Artists’ files are arranged in two categories: members and guest artists, and miscellaneous artists; within each, files are alphabetized by artists' names. To facilitate more compact storage, slides are housed in slide boxes and arranged in the same manner as the artists' files. The one item predating 55 Mercer is a 1939 is a newspaper clipping. Additional information about artist members and guest artists is scattered throughout all other series of 55 Mercer Artists, Inc. records.
  - Miscellaneous Artists (Box 2)
    - Davis, Bruce - Zinnes, Alice; Unidentified, circa 1977-1995; undated (Box 2, Folder 11)
      Davis, Bruce
      Gallagher, Mary
      Glanz, Joy
      Greene, Peter
      Hartnett, Marilu Datoli
      Kerlidou, Gwenael
      Marcellari, John
      Mignon, Roger
      Philbin, Anne
      Resch, Francis X., Jr.
      Ritch, Allison
      Schiff, Ellen
      Schoel, Kim
      Solomon, D. Jack
      Sondheim, Alan
      Zinnes, Alice
      Unidentified
  - Members and Guest Artists Slides (Box 2)
    - Slide Box 1: Ansel, Eric - Cunningham, Bruce, undated (Box 2, Folder 12)
      Ansel, Eric
      Bayer, Arlyne
      Boardman, John
      Berger, Brendt
      Bresnick, Anna Broell
      Briseno, Rolando
      Buchman, Melitte
      Bufano, David
      Capobianco, Dominick
      Charlap, Peter
      Cogswell, Margaret
      Cole, Carolyn
      Corley, Denise
      Crockett, Marilyn
      Cunningham, Bruce
    - Slide Box 2: Cunningham, Bruce, cont'd. - Gregg, Jon, undated (Box 2, Folder 13)
      Derkatsch, Erik
      Dill, Leslie
      Dorman, Josh
      Drum, Sydney
      Fisher, Craig
      Friedman, B.
      Friedman, Barbara
      Gardner, Joan
      Giersbach, Marilyn
      Grant, George (Tom)
      Greenberg, Gloria
      Gregg, Jon
    - Slide Box 3: Gregg, Jon, cont'd. - Karasek, Cynthia, undated (Box 2, Folder 14)
      Harvey, Ian
      Herr, Margo
      Hochhausen, Bill
      Hodgkis, Rosalind
      Hertz, Betti-Sue
      Hewitt, Marsha
      Ideal, Phillis
      Ingram, Lisa
      Jannetti, Tony
      Karasek, Cynthia
    - Slide Box 4: Lable, Eliot - Zimmerman, Salli, undated (Box 2, Folder 15)
      Lable, Eliot
      Landis, M. P.
      Licht, Sydney
      Louaver, Pierre
      Morton, Margaret
      Naito, Jiro
      Olivier, Nancy
      Plansky, Carl
      Robbins, Ed
      Robins, Joyce
      Rosenquist, Marc
      Roth, Richard Lewis
      Rothenberg, Erika
      Schuselka, Elfi
      Steen, Carol J.
      Tardi, Carla
      Unger, Mary Ann
      Walker, Joy
      Wapner, Grace Bakst
      Weider, Ellen
      Whysner, John
      Zimmerman, Salli
  - Miscellaneous Artists Slides (Box 2)
    - Slide Box 5: Andrews, Benny - McCabe, Sigrid, undated (Box 2, Folder 16)
      Andrews, Benny
      Bergson, Don
      Bilik, Paul
      Brenner, Terry
      Chernenko, Anna
      Chevins, Chris
      Davis, Carla
      Edler, Susan
      Epstein, Marina
      Gottsegen, Dan
      Gottsfeld, Linda
      Hirsch, S.
      Hochman, Murray
      Kennedy, Tim
      Kerllidou, Gwenael
      Kisch, Gloria
      Levinson, Peter
      McCabe, Sigrid
    - Slide Box 6: Marcellari, John - Zinnes, Alice; Unidentified, undated (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Financial Records, 1973-2006; Series 4; 0.8 Linear feet Boxes 2-3
  Most financial records concern membership dues, rent and exhibition fees received. Documentation is most comprehensive for the period 1988-2006. This series supplements available membership lists and is a source of information about the titles and dates of exhibitions that may not be included among administrative records (series 1) or exhibition records (series 2). Also included are sporadic banking records, paid bills, insurance and tax records, and treasurers’ reports.
  Additional financial information is interspersed among administrative records (series 1) and exhibition files (series 2).
  - Banking - Citibank Statements and Check Register, 1990-1996 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Banking - Citibank Statements, 1997-2004 (Box 2, Folder 19-20)
  - Banking - First National City Bank Deposits, 1974-1975 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Banking - Union Chelsea National Bank Statements and Cancelled Checks, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Bills Paid, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Bills Paid, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Dues, Rent and Exhibition Fees Received, 1973-1976 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Dues, Rent and Exhibition Fees Received, 1988-1995 (Box 2, Folder 26-32)
  - Dues, Rent and Exhibition Fees Received, 1996-2005 (Box 3, Folder 1-8)
  - Insurance, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Insurance, 1992-2005 (Box 3, Folder 10-12)
  - Tax Returns, Federal and New York State, 1986-2004 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Treasurers' Reports and Budgets, 1984-2006 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Scrapbooks, 1977-1987; Series 5; 0.3 Linear feet Box 3
  Scrapbooks (8 volumes) include exhibition announcements, publicity, reviews, miscellaneous printed material, photographs, and slides. Volumes 1, 4, and 7 appear to be incomplete.
  Seven of the volumes originally were housed in 3-ring binders with acetate sleeves encasing each page. Pages have been removed from the binders and sleeves with the original order retained.
  - Scrapbook 1: Untitled, Disbound, 1979-1980 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Scrapbook 2: "Members, 1980-1981: Non-Photographic Documentation", 1977-1981 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Scrapbook 3: "55 Mercer, 1980-81 Season," Disbound, 1980-1981 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Scrapbook 4: Untitled, Disbound, 1981-1982 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Scrapbook 5: "55 Mercer, 1982-83 Season," Disbound, 1982-1983 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Scrapbook 6: "55 Mercer, 1983-1984" (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Scrapbook 7: "55 Mercer, 1984-1985," Disbound (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Scrapbook 8: "1985-86 at 55 Mercer NYC," Disbound, 1984-1987 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    disbound volume
- Guest Books, 1972-2007; Series 6; 1.7 Linear feet Boxes 3-5
  Guest books, 1972-2007, consist of 22 volumes and loose pages that record gallery visitors, many of whom commented on their reactions to shows. The guest books are an important supplement to the exhibition files, printed material, and administrative records as a source of information about exhibitions. Although there are some obvious gaps, this may be the most complete series of the 55 Mercer Artists, Inc. records.
  - Loose Pages, 1972 February-1976 January (Box 3, Folder 23-26)
  - Volume 1: 1977 September - 1978 January, 1977-1978 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Volume 2: 1980 March - 1981 November, 1980-1981 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Volume 3: 1981 December - 1984 August, 1981-1984 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Volumer 4: 1985 June - 1988 June, 1985-1988 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Volume 5: 1988 June - 1989 February, 1988-1989 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Volume 6: 1989 February - 1990 February, 1989-1990 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Volume 7: 1991 January - November (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Volume 8: 1991 November - 1993 March (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Volume 9: 1993 April - 1994 April, 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Volume 10: 1997 September - 1998 June, 1999-2000 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Volume 11: 1998 September - 1999 May, 1998-1999 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Volume 12: 1999 June-2000 January (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Volume 13: 2000 January - August (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Volume 14: 2000 August - 2001 February, 2000-2001 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Volume 15: 2001 February - October (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Volume 16: 2002 September - 2003 September, 2002-2003 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Volume 17: 2003 October - 2004 March, 2003-2004 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Volume 18: 2004 March - 2005 April, 2004-2005 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Volume 19: 2005 April - 2006 January, 2005-2006 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Volume 20: 2006 January (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Volume 21: 2007 January - August (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Volume 22 and Loose Pages, undated (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Printed Material, 1973-2007; Series 7; 0.9 Linear feet Box 5, OV 6
  Printed material consists mainly of exhibition announcements, catalogs and publicity produced by 55 Mercer Artists, Inc. It seems likely that announcements and press releases may not have been printed for every exhibition, especially in the earliest years; there is little doubt that copies of every exhibition announcement, catalog, and press release issued have not survived. Other printed material consists of articles about or mentioning 55 Mercer Artists, Inc., exhibition reviews, advertisements and event listings.
  Artists' files (series 3) and scrapbooks (series 4) also include printed material.
  - 55 Mercer Exhibition Announcements, Catalogs and Publicity, 1973-1979 (Box 5, Folder 8-20)
    Oversized material housed in OV 6
  - Articles About or Mentioning 55 Mercer; Reviews, 1976-2000; undated (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Adverisements and Events Listings, undated (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Oversize Exhibition Announcements, Catalogs and Publicity, 1976-1999; undated (Box OV 6)
    from Box 5, Folders 8-11, 14, 20
- Members and Guest Artists (Box 1)
  - Alexander, Bette - Brandt, Andreas, undated; 1975-2003 (Box 1, Folder 63)
    Alexander, Bette
    Amdur, Margery
    Barnard, Anne
    Baroff, Jill
    Beardman, John
    Biro, Ivan
    Brandt, Andreas
  - Bresnick, Anna Broell, undated; 1987-2006 (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - Bressler, Martin - Capobianco, D., circa 1981-circa 1983 (Box 1, Folder 65)
    Bressler, Martin
    Cann, David
    Capobianco, D.
  - Cavaliere, Corliss, undated; circa 2002-2006 (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - Charlap, Peter, undated; 1989-2005 (Box 1, Folder 67)
  - Coffey, Susanna - Derkatsch, Erik, circa 1982-1997; undated (Box 1, Folder 68)
    Coffey, Susanna
    De Ricco, Hank
  - Dorman, Joshua, 1995-1996; undated (Box 1, Folder 69)
  - Drum, Sydney, undated; 1992-2006 (Box 1, Folder 70)